It's been a while.
久しぶりですね
yes.
はい
long time no see.
久 しぶり
久しぶり
How have you been?
元気だった?
I'm not feeling well.
元気じゃない
Aren't you feeling well?
元気じゃないの?
fine.
元気
元 気
There are times when I don't feel well.
元気じゃない時もあるよね
After all, they are humans.
やっぱり人間だからね
what have you been up to?
何してたの?
Were you always interested in women?
女にばっかりしてたの?
I don't do that much.
そんなにしてないの
Haven't you done that much?
そんなにしてないの?
That's right.
そうなんだ
nice.
いいね
I'm wearing a maid outfit today.
今日メイド服だよ
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくない?
That's dangerous.
やばいよね
You're going to have sex with the maid.
メイドでセックスしちゃうよね
This camera is your master today.
今日はこのカメラがご主人様
good?
いい?
Is it okay because what your husband says is absolutely true?
ご主人様の言うことは絶対だからいいですか?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
There's an indoor microscope here.
室内顕微鏡がここにあるんですけど
It's scary though.
怖いんだけど
But you saw it earlier, right?
でもさっき見たでしょ?
Isn't it interesting?
面白いでしょ?
this.
これ
But you've never seen Macon, have you?
でもマコンなんか見たことないでしょ?
By yourself.
自分で
do not have.
ない
Now you can see it.
これで見れるんだよ
Isn't this amazing?
これ、すごくない?
So you can see inside the Macon.
それでマコンの中見れるんだよ
Can I insert this directly?
これ直接入れるの?
Oh, put that Cusco in there.
ああ、あのクスコ入れて
Does it make a whirring sound?
ってヒューってするの?
Huh.
ヒューって
And it's electric.
しかもそれ電気つくからさ
You can see all the way to the inside.
中まで丸見えなんだよ
Do you want to see my urethra too?
俺の尿道も見る?
How do I see it?
どうやって見るの?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
there is nothing.
何もない
That hurts, huh?
痛いもん、あれ
I can't see the urethra, this.
尿道見んないし、これ
It hurts, it looks painful.
痛い、痛そう
That's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いよ、それ
Kin looks like he's going to stand up soon.
キ ン コすぐ立っちゃいそう
nice.
いいね
Do you know it yourself?
自分でも分かってる?
That's right.
だよね
That's right, you understand.
そうだよね、分かるよね
This is amazing no matter who sees it.
これ誰が見てもすごいいいよ、これ
I think this angle is perfect.
このアングルとかもう完璧だと思うの
No, no, just a little.
いや いやいや、ちょっと
Look at this angle.
見てごらん、このアングル
copper?
どう?
Oh, I guess this is it.
お、こうかな
Well, I can't see it.
あ ん ま 見えないね、俺
Oh, my eyesight is bad.
あ、目悪いんだ
Please stand up for a moment.
ちょっと立ってみて
Wow, nice.
うわ、いいね
It's amazing when you stand up.
立つと立つとで素晴らしい
It's powerful and wide-ranging.
迫 力が広いね
ERROR
これ電車の中でガタンゴトーンっていう感じでメイド服
Don't you want to make a clunky tone with a maid outfit?
メイド服でガタンゴトーンしないか?
I can still tell if it's a sailor uniform, but I can't tell if it's a maid costume.
セーラー服ならまだ分かるけど、メイド服じゃ分かんないよね
You don't.
しないよね
Can you move back a bit?
ちょっと後ろいい?
Awesome.
すげー
It's a tea bag.
テ ィーバックだね
That's amazing, T-Bag.
すごいね、ティーバック
Pussy.
おまんこ
Pussy, pussy there.
お まんこ、そこおまんこ
That's your pussy, right?
そこおまんこでしょ
Just try your hand at it.
ちょっとそこ手ついてみて
There.
そ こに
Show me your butt.
お尻見せて
nice.
いいね
This is really good.
すごくいいよ、これ
Look here.
こっち見て
This shows off your butt.
これお尻丸見えだよ
I'd like to keep it like this from now on.
このまま入れたいね、ここからは
I guess it's like this.
こういう感じかな
This is nice.
これいいな
It feels good to put it in like this.
こうやって入れる感じいいね
I think I'll try putting it in.
入れてみようかな
That's amazing.
すごいな
Her butt is so impressive.
お尻の迫力半端ね
This is amazing.
すごいな、これ
Do you usually have tea bags?
普 段からティーバック?
Do you usually drink tea bags?
普段からティーバックなの?
Why are you in there?
なんで入ってんの?
Did you come in special today?
今日は特別入ってきちゃったの?
I worked extra hard.
特別 頑張ったんだ
That's right.
そうなんだ
Wow, the maid outfit is really good.
いいっすね、メイド服は本当に
In the future, yes.
将来、そうだな
If you decide to hire a maid,
メイドさんとか雇うことになったら、
ERROR
こういうの着るのかな?
actually.
実際に
I wonder what it is?
どうなんだろう?
Will I wear it?
着るのかな?
I don't know.
分からん
分からないよね
What do you like most?
何が一番好き?
cooked rice.
ご飯
Hamburger.
ハンバーグ
Hamburger?
ハンバーグ?
Do you like meat?
お肉好きなの?
I can only eat meat.
お肉しか食べれない
Can you only eat meat?
お肉しか食べれないの?
What about rice?
ご飯は?
bread.
パン
bread?
パ ン?
So, do you like hamburgers?
じゃ、ハンバーガー好き?
I like hamburgers.
ハンバーガー好き
Do you like McDonald's hamburgers?
マクドナルドのハンバーグ好き?
like.
好き
I like it.
好きなんだ
What is the first kitchen?
ファーストキッチンは?
I've never been to First Kitchen.
ファーストキッチン行ったことない
ファーストキッチン行ったことないんだ
What is it in America?
アメリカにある、なんだっけ?
I forgot the name.
名前忘れちゃった
There's a really delicious hamburger restaurant.
すげえおいしいハンバーガー屋さんがあるんだよね
Burger King?
バーガーキング?
Not.
じゃない
Burger somehow.
なんとかバーガー
It's really delicious, I went to America and tried it.
すごくおいしいんだよ、行ってみてたからアメリカを
cute.
可愛い
Let's go for that, for that.
そのために、そのために行ってみようよ
Oh, it's really good to rinse.
おー、やっぱすがうのがいいわ
nice.
いいね
cute.
可愛い
That's good.
いいっすね
Can I stand again then?
じゃあもう一回立っていい?
Standing when it's not cheap.
安くない時の立ってるし
That's really it.
本当にあれだわ
It does look similar to that.
やっぱあれに似てるよね
To Tanakarena.
タナカレーナにね
I'm not happy at all.
全然嬉しくない
why?
なんで?
I really like Tanakarena.
俺めっちゃ好きなんだけどタナカレーナ
No?
ダメ?
I'm not happy at all.
全然嬉しくない
Aren't you happy?
嬉しくない?
Now, let's get into the bag position from earlier.
じゃあそのままさっきのバッグの体勢になろう
You can try it again.
もう一回手ついていいよ
Look here.
こっち見て
Yes, that's it.
そう、それそれ
That's it, that's it.
それだよそれ
This is amazing.
これすごい
Keep looking at me, looking at the camera.
ずっと見ててね、カメラ目線ね
This this this this.
これこれこれこれ
It's such a beautiful color.
すごい色いんだよね
Please watch it.
見ててね
Okay, let's get into this position.
よし、きたぜこの体勢
copper?
どう?
This is terrible in a maid costume.
メイド服でこれ、やばい
Your pants are completely visible.
パンツ丸見えだよ
close.
近い
It's completely visible.
丸見えだよ
How do I get this out?
これどうやってぶら取るんだろう?
I don't think you can get it off without some whirring from behind.
後ろからヒューってしないと取れないと思う
Is that so?
そうなの?
Then come a little earlier.
じゃあちょっと前に来て
Can I take it?
取っていい?
Do you coo?
クーって引くの?
You can get the ribbon.
リボンが取れる
sorry.
ご めん
Bring it back.
戻せよ
Can I put it back?
戻していい?
Are you going to put it back?
戻すの?
Can't you get it?
取れないの?
Can't you get it if I put it back?
戻したら取れない?
If I put it back, I can't get it.
戻したら取れないよ
Because I can't see this.
だってこれ見れないもんね
You can't see her boobs from above.
この上からおっぱいぶら見れないもんね
I can't see it.
見れない
Can't you see my boobs?
おっぱいも見れなくね?
I can't see it.
見れない
That's an amazing maid costume.
すごいメイド服だね、それ
I have to lower it all.
全部下げないと
That's right.
そうなんだ
Is that what it feels like?
そういう感じ?
That's how it feels.
そういう感じ
Is that what it feels like?
そういう感じか
What should I do?
どうしよう
I can't see it.
見れないんだ
Ah, but it's a big deal.
あー、でもせっかく
I wonder what it is?
どうなんだろう?
I wonder if everyone wears maid costumes as they are?
メイド服ってみんなぶらしてまんまやんのかな?
Ah, the bell is transparent, though.
あ、ベル透けてるね、でもね
Somewhat.
若干
What, isn't there?
え、ないの?
Where to bring it forward.
前出すところ
There's nothing to put forward.
前出すところない
I have no choice but to know.
知るしかない
Then let's take it.
じゃあ取っちゃおう
The maid grabbed it.
メイドさんがぶら取った
Oh, my dick came out.
お、チクビ出てきた
Chikubi.
チクビ
A tingle came out.
チクビ出てきたよ
Grind.
ゴリゴリ
So let's cut it again.
じゃあもう一回切っちゃおう
Shall I cut it again?
もう一回切るの?
As expected, I'll be wearing a maid outfit until the very end today.
やっぱり今日はずっと最後までメイド服だな
Is it okay?
いいの?
Ah, okay.
あー、いいよ
Okay.
いいよ
This, right here?
これね、ここ?
Chikubi?
チクビ?
this?
これ?
yes?
そう?
Yeah.
うん
You're standing still.
チクビ立ってるね
Maid's pants.
メイドさんのパンツ
Oh, maid.
お、メイドさん
Maid, this is super erotic.
メイドさん、これ超エロいじゃん
That's terrible.
やばいね
That's amazing.
すごいよ
This is super erotic.
超エロい、これ
That's terrible.
やばいな
The maid's pussy, here.
メイドさんのオマンコスか、ここ
The maid's...here.
メイドさんの...ここだね
Don't you get horny when you touch this area?
ここ触るとムラムラしてこない?
Will you come?
してくる?
It's so erotic here.
めっちゃエロい、ここ
In a maid outfit.
メイド服で
No.
ダメだよ
Because you'll get wet.
濡れてきちゃうから
Be gentle at first.
最初は優しくね
Why?
なんでだろう?
Where is it?
何処だろう?
Something that feels good.
気持ちいいやつ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Is it moving?
動いちゃってる?
Looking so happy.
すごい嬉しい格好
Maid uniform pants.
メイド服のパンツ
Yeah.
うん
how was it?
どうだった?
Korya-chan?
こりゃちゃん?
terrible.
や ばい
It's direct pressure.
直接圧じゃん
Something direct?
なんか直接の?
What's right?
何が当たってる?
This is correct.
こりゃちゃん当たってるよ
I'm in trouble.
困るよ
Wow, that's terrible.
うわ、やばい
Twirling is dangerous.
くるくるやばい
Round and round.
くるくる
Do you know anything?
何か知ってる?
Where?
どこに?
Okay.
いいよ
Also the back of these pants.
このパンツの裏も
Show me the inside of your pants.
パンツの裏見せて
why?
なんで?
Show me the inside of your pants.
パンツの裏見せて
No.
ダメだよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいな
See you later.
後で見る
I'll see one more person.
後1人見とく
Okay, okay.
よし、オッケー
My pussy has come out.
出 てきたよ、マンコは
What should I do?
どうするの?
this.
これ
I have to preach.
お説教しないと
Maid.
メイドさん
I have to preach about the maid's pussy.
メイドさんのマンコ説教しないとね
I have to preach today.
今日は説教していかないとね
I have to look inside her pussy properly.
マンコの中ちゃんと見なきゃいけないから
Why are you sleeping?
なんで寝てるの?
I'm sleeping.
寝てるよ
what happened?
どうしたの?
this.
これ
Why are you sleeping?
どうして寝てるの?
なんで寝てるの?
Why?
どうして?
Because it feels good?
気持ちいいから?
Did you fall asleep because it felt so good?
気持ちいいから寝ちゃったの?
Is it okay here?
ここ はいい?
In the back, this is terrible.
奥、やばい
Oh, it's been 2 minutes.
あ、2分入っちゃった
Oh, I've been in for 2 minutes.
あ、2分入ってきた
here yes
ここはい
stomach?
い?
My pussy is a mess.
マ ンコ、ぐっちゃぐちゃ
My pussy is so wet
マ ンコ、ぐっちゃぐ
tea.
ちゃ
It became a huge mess.
め っちゃぐちゃぐちゃになっちゃった
That's amazing.
すごいよ
A lot of juice came out.
汁がいっぱい出てきちゃった
Well then, let's take a look inside her pussy.
じゃあ、マンコの中見ていこうかな
good?
いい?
Huh?
あれ?
yes.
そう
First, I'm going to put my pussy in it.
まず、マンコを入れていくよ
May I?
いいですか?
Maid.
メイドさん
It's all over.
す っぽりだね
Which one should I go with?
どっちでいったほうがいいんだろうな?
Is it spreading?
広がってる?
It's okay, right?
大丈夫でしょ?
I feel like it's spreading.
広がってる気がする
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Let's go.
いこう
Let's take a look inside.
中見ていこう
scared.
怖い
I'll take a look.
見ていくよ
There's electricity on.
電気ついてるよね
It's scary though.
怖いんだけど
I'll take a look inside.
中見ていくからね
It's completely visible.
すげえ丸見えだね
I can see it.
見えてるね
Watch this on the monitor.
これをモニター越しで
The top is amazing.
上がなんかすごい
Shall we take a look?
見ていこうか
That's difficult.
難しいな
It's reflecting, isn't it?
反射してるんだよね、光が
amazing.
すごい
Can you see it?
見えてる?
Feels good.
いい感じ
Can you see it in this brightness?
この明るさだったら見えるかな?
Okay okay.
オッケーオッケー
So can you see it for yourself?
じゃあ、自分で見れる?
It's kind of uneven.
なんか凸凹してる
Awesome.
すげえ
You can really see it.
めっちゃ見えてるじゃん
amazing.
すごい
That's amazing.
すごいね
what?
何?
This guy.
このこいつ
That's it.
それあれだよ
No, no.
違う違う
I don't know.
む ずい
let's see?
どれどれ?
Is that the best uterus?
あれが一番子宮?
The uterus is in the back.
奥が子宮
The inside is the uterus.
中が子宮ですね
Huh?
あれ?
Oh yeah, that's the uterus.
そうそう、あれ子宮
This is the uterus.
これが子宮
I can't get in anymore.
これ以上入らない
Impossible due to size.
大きさ的に無理
It looks like a hole.
なんか穴みたいになってる
Yes, it looks like a hole.
そう、穴みたいになってるでしょ
why?
なんで?
What is that?
あれ何?
This is the uterus.
これが子宮
Sperm enters here and separates into left and right,
ここに精子が入って、左右に分かれて、
If it reaches the egg, it means you can have a child.
卵子に届いたら子供ができるってこと
I have to go this far anyway, right?
ここまでとりあえず行かなきゃいけないんだよね、
Sperm.
精子が
But it looks like a cylinder.
でもさ、気筒みたいだよね
That's really it.
ほんとそれ
Yes, it looks like there's some kind of dick in it.
そう、なんかチンコ入ってるみたい
Humans are amazing.
すごいよね人間って
Doesn't it look like a dick?
チンコみたいじゃない?
this.
これ
Looks like a dick.
チンコみたい
First time seeing it?
初めて見た?
How do you feel?
どんな気分?
Looks like a dick.
チンコみたい
My bottom is really loose.
なんかすごい下が ビラビラしてる
Is this what it is?
これ が、あれ?
This isn't below.
これ下じゃないよ
Oh, is this the one above?
あ、上これ?
Look at it like this.
これ こういう風に見るんだ
Sorry, wait, how's your pussy?
ご めん待って、マンコどう?
It's a pussy, so enter it like this.
マンコだから、こう入ってくんだ
Yes, it feels like this.
そう、こういう感じ
Ah, then something on the side.
あ、じゃあ横のなんか
Yes, the side part.
そう、横の部分
The sides are so creamy.
横がトロトロってなってるんだ
It's actually on the Jispot.
本当はジスポット上にある
It's really white though.
めっちゃ白いんだけど
This is the pussy from earlier.
これはさっきのおマンコ
Painted sticker.
塗れたシール
It's okay.
大丈夫ですね
He doesn't seem to be sick.
病気はなさそうですね
Isn't that what you're testing?
っていう感じで検査するんじゃない?
Well, there's something.
いや、なんかあるじゃん
Wouldn't something like disease testing be a good idea?
病気検査とかこういうのもいいんじゃないの?
I don't know though.
わかんないけど
That's amazing.
すごいね
feel ill.
気持ち悪い
I feel like I'm crying.
なんか泣いてるんだよね
What is the uterus?
子宮って
Yes, my uterus is crying.
そうだ ね、子宮が泣いてる
Then hold on for a while.
じゃあちょっと持ってて
What I want to check with this is what will happen if I guess.
これでちょっとチェックしたいのが 当てるとどうなるっていう
In this state.
この状態でね
Hold it, please.
持っててね、ちゃんと
When it hits Bri-chan.
ブリちゃんに当たると
copper?
どう?
this.
これ
Bri-chan, are you right?
ブリちゃん、当たってる?
It feels good.
気持ちいいよ
Please be honest.
素直になってってね
It's expanding rapidly.
どんどん膨張してってる
Is it expanding?
膨張してるの?
Look at the top.
上側、ほら
This is it, oh, I see.
これね、あ、そっか
I don't know if this is it.
これだとわかんないな
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
I'll change Cusco a little once.
一回、クスコをちょっと チェンジするね
I think it's better to lay Cusco down.
クスコを横にしたほうがいいな
I'll lay it down.
横にするね
Lay it down like this.
こう 横にする
It doesn't hurt.
痛くないよね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I think it's probably okay, not at all.
多分大丈夫だと思う、全然
You should watch Cusco as he lays down.
クスコを横にしていくとこを 見ていたほうがいいな
The part where Cusco is laid down might be very important.
クスコを横にするところ すごい大事かも
why?
なんで?
I was able to see it.
見てもらえた
It's got Cusco in it, right?
ク スコ入ってるでしょ
I'll lay it down.
横にしていくよ
Look, the J-spot has appeared.
ほら、ジェイスポット出てきた
which one?
どれ?
The one above.
上のやつ
Amazing, amazing.
すごい、すごい
which one?
どれ?
Which is up?
上ってどっち?
This, this, this.
これ、これ、これ
Now that my pussy is shaped like this, it's going to come in like this.
今こういうおまんこの形だから こう入ってくるじゃん
We have the same spot.
同じスポットがある
That's J Spot.
それがジェイスポットなんだ
Is this correct?
これ、当たってる?
hot?
暑い?
That's hot.
暑いよ、それ
It was hot.
暑かった
sorry.
ごめん
Now, have it.
これで、 持ってて
Take a guess.
ちょっと当ててね
What will happen?
どうなる?
It moves, right?
動くね?
Looks like it's going to stick.
くっつきそう
It looks like it's going to stick, you know.
くっつきそうだよ、ほら
It looks like we're going to stick together.
くっついちゃいそう
Wow, it looks like it's going to stick.
すごい、くっつきそう
Look.
ほ ら
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
気 持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
It stuck, it stuck.
くっついた、くっついた
It stuck, didn't it?
くっついたよね
It's going to stick, it's going to stick.
くっついちゃう、くっついちゃう
This is amazing.
すごいね、これ
We'll stick together.
くっついちゃう
picture?
え?
copper?
どう?
This statue of a dead person.
この死人像
You can see the urethra.
尿道見えてるじゃん
左側、左上
Urethral?
尿道?
That's the urethra.
尿道だよ、それ
this?
これ?
This part.
ここの部分
There's a hole in this.
これ、穴入ってんじゃん
This is the urethra.
これ、尿道
It's the urethra.
尿道だよ
Yes, that's the urethra.
そうそう、それ尿道
It looks like some juice is dripping.
なんか汁が垂れてきそう
terrible.
やばい
That's amazing.
すごいな
It's mysterious.
神秘的だね
Don't go any deeper.
もっと奥まで入んないで
hang on.
待って
It's hot.
熱いね
It's hot, it's so hot.
熱いよ、めちゃくちゃ
Look, it's not hot.
ほら、熱くないよ
Would you like to touch it?
触ってみ?
Look.
ほら
Don't guess.
当てないように
It's in.
入ってる
Can't you see?
見えない?
It's so wet.
すごい濡れてる
It's white.
白いね
This one is white.
この中、白いな
It's so white.
すごい白い
Very wet.
すごい濡れ濡れ
hot.
熱い
hot?
熱い?
Isn't it warm?
あったかくない?
Looks like Vero.
ベロみたいだね
This is amazing.
すごいよ、これ
I don't understand seeing it like this.
こう見るのは分かんないな
I don't understand if you look at it like this.
こう見ると分かんないね
Is it better on the side?
やっぱ横のほうがいいのかな?
it hurts.
痛い
it hurts?
痛い?
it hurts.
痛い
I'll take it once.
一回じゃあ取るね
It's easier to see this way.
こっちのほうが見やすいね
I'd like to see it if I put sperm in it.
精 子入れたら見てみたいな
I want to see the sperm inside.
精 子入ってるところ見たいな
Can I see it there?
あそこにあっててみていい?
picture?
え?
No way.
やだ
Sperm is coming out.
精子出てる
It's not sperm.
精子じゃない
What is this white?
この白いの何?
Can I just check what it's like?
どんな感じかちょっと チェックしていい?
What does it feel like?
ど んな感じか?
どんな感じ?
How does it feel?
どんな感じですか?
feel ill.
気持ち悪い
It's cloudy.
曇っちゃった
It stayed on when it was cloudy.
曇ったらずっとついたんだよ
Did something happen?
なんかついたのかな?
Absolutely, right?
絶対そうでしょ
Something happened to me.
なんかついちゃった
I can't see it.
見えないな
What happened?
なった?
It was cloudy.
曇ったよ
picture?
え?
Is it cloudy?
曇った?
It's inside the maid's pussy.
メイドさんの おまんこの中ですね
It's cloudy.
曇っちゃったな
Because I'm going to put it on.
つけるからだよ
Something happened to me.
なんかついちゃったね
That's amazing, though.
すごいね、でも
It's beautiful on the side.
横とかきれいじゃん
Why are you beating me up?
な にこのボコボコして
Do you want to do it?
る の?
Look, there are two dancing.
ほら、 2個踊ってる
Are you going?
いっちゃうの?
Ah, let's go.
あ、いく
go?
いく?
Okay.
いい よ
Oh, has it decreased?
あ、減っちゃった?
Look, Kuri-chan.
クリちゃんほら
Kuri-chan, look, isn't it amazing?
クリちゃんがほら、 すごくな?
here.
ここ
terrible.
やばい
Kuri-chan is standing.
ク リ ちゃん立ってる
Boo, are you gone?
ぶー、行っちゃったの?
Have you gone?
行っちゃった?
how was it?
どうだった?
Is Beld-san strong?
ベルドさん強い?
Awesome, Kuri-chan is standing up?
すごい、クリちゃん立つの?
Kuri-chan will stand.
クリちゃん立つよ
You're standing up really well.
すごい立ってんじゃん
Kuri-chan is standing up amazingly.
クリちゃんすごい立ってるよ
terrible.
やばい
amazing.
すごい
Gundachi, gundachi.
ガ ンダチだ、ガンダチ
scared.
怖い
The maid: Maid, please clean my dick.
メイドさんが、 メイドさん、 俺のチンチンきれいにしてね
It's a maid.
メイドさんだ
メイドさんだね
yeah?
ん?
Okay.
いいよ
Sleep with your skin on.
皮被ってる状態で眠って
why?
なんで?
At first.
最 初は
While watching it first.
最 初に見ながら
Huh, did it get bigger?
え、チンチン大きくなった?
Okay.
おっけー
already.
もう
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
Oh, this is better.
お、こっちの方がいいじゃん
It's in my nose.
鼻の中にいる
This, pat Riod.
これ、リオードを撫でて
Okay, lick it.
いいよ、舐めて
appear?
見える?
Can you see it yet?
もう見える?
Great, look at it from here.
すごい、こっちから見る
Really amazing.
ほんと、すごい
Wow, it looks great.
すごい、いい感じに映ってるんだよね
I'll do it.
やってあげる
What do you mean?
ってこと?
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
cute.
かわいい
I can't see it though.
見えないんだけど
Can't you see?
見えない?
You can see it, right?
映ってるでしょ?
Isn't it visible?
映ってない?
Isn't this the angle?
この角度じゃない?
Just a little more, like this.
もうちょっと、こう
Ah, quite a bit.
あ、そこそこ
Ah, this is it.
あ、これだな
Now give me a blowjob, just a little.
これでフェラ、ちょっとして
Look.
ほら
You can see it, right?
映ってるでしょ?
Hmph.
ふんふん
close.
近い
It's close though.
近いんだけど
It's close.
近いよ
Awesome, maid.
すげえ、メイドさん
Okay, let's go to bed.
よし、ベッド行こう
Oh, nice, maid.
お、いいね、メイド
When they grow up, they'll get colder and colder.
大きくなったら、 綺麗に寒くなっていっているよ
yes.
はい
appear?
見える?
What if I want it?
欲しくなったら?
Yeah.
うん
Yeah?
うん?
Please master.
お主人様ください
cute.
かわいい
Do you want me to see it?
見えて欲しい?
Yeah.
うん
I can see it.
映るもん
I'm already aware of it.
もう気づいてるよ
Yeah, that's it.
うん、それで
Ah, that's where I came in.
あ、そこに入ってきた
Come in.
入ってきて
Look at the camera.
カメラ見て
Okay, so let's come and do this.
よし、じゃあ来るって、こうやってしようか
I feel like leaving.
行っちゃいそうになる
I'm seriously tempted to go there.
マジで行っちゃいそうになるよ
Why?
なん でだろう
pack,
パ ック、
I feel like I'm going to go there.
行 っちゃいそうになっちゃう
It's a big hit, isn't it?
すごく当たるでしょ
break.
休憩
I feel like leaving.
行っちゃいそうになる
I feel like I'm seriously going to go there.
マジで行っちゃいそうになる
I'm not good at Puck.
パック、苦手なんだよね
I'll put it in.
入れるよ
I think I can fill it up, pussy.
いっぱい入れそう、マンコ
I'm going with a stud press.
種付けプレスで行くね
Can I go with a seeding press?
種付けプレスで行っていい?
Raise your feet a little.
ちょっと足を上げて
Looks like it's coming out.
出てきそう
nice.
いいね
Come out, come out.
出てくる、出てくる
Just a little more.
あとちょっと
It's coming out.
出てきてる
It really came out.
めっちゃ出たさ
It's so white.
すごい白い
I'm going to sleep a lot, pussy.
いっぱい寝そう、マンコ
Go to sleep.
寝しろ
That's a betrayal job.
あれ、 betrayal 仕 事
I'm not doing that though.
して るんじゃないけどね
Okay, goddamn!
いい よ、 goddamn!
dings dinging аль dinging looking for
dings dinging аль dinging 探して
Let's go, pussy.
行 っちゃうよ、マンコ
This stillness is so beautiful.
この静止すごい綺麗なんだけど
I am so beautifully still.
俺こんな綺麗な静止なんだ
You can do this anywhere.
どこでもできるな、これは
It came out, it came out.
出てきた出てきた
Raise your strength one more time.
もう一発力上げて
Oh, it's dripping, it's dripping.
おー、垂れてきた垂れてきた
It stuck to my butt.
お尻にくっついた
nice.
いいね
It's a waste so I put it inside.
もったいないから中にしまって
It stuck to my butt.
お 尻 に く っついた
So let's clean up for the last time.
じゃあ最後お掃除しよう
Let's finish by cleaning.
お掃除で終わりにしよう
What does your pussy taste like?
自分のマンコの どんな味する?
sour.
酸っぱい
sour?
酸っぱい?
lie?
嘘?
I don't know, I wonder what it is.
わかんない、なんだろう
Don't you know?
わか んない?
Okay, then one last thing.
よし、じゃあちょっと最後
Let me conclude with some final thoughts.
最後感想を言って終わりにしよう
bad?
まずい?
Was it bad?
まずかった?
Because it feels like my own pussy.
自分のマンコな感じだからね
How was your cosplay?
どう でした、コスプレー?
how was it?
どうだった?
No, I was pretty excited.
いや、興奮したわ、俺だいぶ
pretty.
かなり
nice.
いいね
I was actually thinking of going with the rear view, but
本当は背面気象で行こうかなって思ったんだけど、
I couldn't stand my stillness.
耐えられなかった、俺の静止が
The pink color is too tight.
ピンクが締まりが良すぎて
So what are you going to do next?
じゃあ今度何でやるんですか?
Nance next time.
今度ナンス
Nance, that's right.
ナンス、そうだね
I bought a nonce.
ナンス買ったんだよね
Let's do it with nonce, then.
ナンスでやろう、じゃあ
Well then, see you next time.
じゃあ 次回ナンスで
So let's do it again.
じゃあまたやりましょう
So say goodbye with both hands.
じゃあ両手バイバイで
Let's say goodbye with a smile.
笑顔でバイバイしましょうか
Let's say goodbye with the best smile.
最高の笑顔でバイバイしよう
bye bye.
バイバイ
Well then, good night.
じゃあね、おやすみなさい